<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>services on Gantry</title>
    <link>https://gantry.cloud/categories/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in services on Gantry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gantry.cloud/categories/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/services/</guid>
      <description>Terraform + Kubernetes + Prometheus + Helm Foundation Your infrastructure scalability needs now go beyond what can be accomplished with docker-compose. We will build your helm charts and give you a documented process for setting up your infrastructure on a cloud provider such as Gcloud, AWS, DigitalOcean or Azure.
What we provide:
 Main.tf file tailored to create the resources for your services (load balancers, clusterIPs, Pods) Unified or volumed helm charts templating your deployments Deployment script to launch those services in a kubernetes cluster Prometheus dashboard installed to view your status Documentation on how to recreate and maintain system  $15,000 up to 20 microservices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/products/</guid>
      <description>Enhanced Kubernetes Managed and self-hosted options available
Enhanced CI/CD Managed and self-hosted options available
So Kubernetes is your destination, great choice! Now how do you get there? Whether you are deploying an API, UI, or Machine Learning Model, you still need to progress through the software development lifecycle.
Here automation is your friend, with Continuous Integration and Continuous delivery you can increase feature and reliability development velocity for your application. With each commit you can build, test, deliver, and monitor your product.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
