<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>services on Gantry</title>
    <link>https://gantry.cloud/categories/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in services on Gantry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gantry.cloud/categories/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/services/</guid>
      <description>Terraform + Kubernetes + Prometheus + Helm Foundation Your infrastructure scalability needs now go beyond what can be accomplished with docker-compose. We will build your helm charts and give you a documented process for setting up your infrastructure on a cloud provider such as Gcloud, AWS, DigitalOcean or Azure.
What we provide:
 Main.tf file tailored to create the resources for your services (load balancers, clusterIPs, Pods) Unified or volumed helm charts templating your deployments Deployment script to launch those services in a kubernetes cluster Prometheus dashboard installed to view your status Documentation on how to recreate and maintain system  Implemenation of Declarative Git-Ops Pipeline (ARGOCD) Don&amp;rsquo;t push code to your cluster, have your cluster intelligently pull it instead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/products/</guid>
      <description>Sonar Vulnerability Scanning CI pipeline vulnerability scanning system incorporating SonarCube, Jenkins, Jira, and Git to prevent vulnerable source code from deploying into dev, test, or production. See the demo dashboard analyze our own infrastructure as well as the industry-standard OWASP-Vulnerable Web Application Xero Bring best practices surrounding reliability, security and efficiency to your infrastructure with our agent, logic engine, and dashboard built on cutting edge and trusted open source.  Explained by Master SRE, Jason Stryker   Explained from the perspective of a business owner   Explained from the perspective of a software manager   Explained by Engineer, Mark   High-Level Overview </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
