<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Gantry</title>
    <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Gantry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:19:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gantry.cloud/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Argo Explained</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/argoexplained/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:19:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/argoexplained/</guid>
      <description>   Lets get seven points clear:  Argo is a free, open-source continuous deployment tool It&amp;rsquo;s designed to be easy to use and deploy with any language or framework It works by running commands on your servers as you push new code to GitHub You can configure it for automatic deployments using web hooks from GitHub or BitBucket When deploying, Argo will run tests before updating the server if necessary If tests fail, then no changes are made and the previous version of the app remains deployed until you manually update it yourself (or fix the tests) Argo also has an option for staging environments that let you test out new features before they go live in production  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Kickstart</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/kickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 14:43:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/kickstart/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes Kickstart will take your existing application built in docker containers and load them into a scalable kubernetes cluster. We&amp;rsquo;ll provide documentation on how to scale and debug deployments alongside our team taking care of the infrastructure tier specifics. Our four week pilot study will bring your infrastructure stack up-to-date while you continue iterating with your developers uninterrupted. Get started right away or contact us for questions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are you bringing aboard?</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/gantry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/gantry/</guid>
      <description>Straddled over a shipyard, a Gantry Crane is used to organize containers, and is capable of lifting the heaviest loads on the planet. In our increasingly automated world, infrastructure is code, software is containerized, and storage is cloud based. Your business has deadlines, objectives and assets that need to get places on time, every time. Let us do the heavy lifting. – Gantry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kustomize</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/kustomize/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 20:45:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/kustomize/</guid>
      <description>About Kustomize </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Zero</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/dayzero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/dayzero/</guid>
      <description>Day Zero: Your team has decided that it is time to move virtual. There are questions whose answers only create more questions. What platform? Which Software? Who will handle it? What if it breaks? And most critical: What if we lose critical data? Start at the beginning and follow the map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decisions</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/decisions/</guid>
      <description>Decision Making How do you decide what cloud is for you?
Do you need compliance? Perhaps you are leaning towards Azure.
Are your engineers on google? GCloud!
Maybe you need your own control planes altogether!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managed CI Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/managed-ci-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/managed-ci-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>So Kubernetes is your destination, great choice! Now how do you get there? Whether you are deploying an API, UI, or Machine Learning Model, you still need to progress through the software development lifecycle.
Here automation is your friend, with Continuous Integration and Continuous delivery you can increase feature and reliability development velocity for your application. With each commit you can build, test, deliver, and monitor your product.
With our managed CI/CD pipelines we provide you with the latest cloud native build, test, and delivery techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A company taking flight</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/skygrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/skygrid/</guid>
      <description>A small team of engineers on a big mission to make the sky a safer, more efficient space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argo CD</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/argocd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/argocd/</guid>
      <description>Why not declarative? Have you ever written a deploy script to push your Kubernetes Helm chart yamls up to the cluster one by one?
Maybe you do this manually and then have the misfortune of having to do it all over once more when something breaks.
ArgoCD is a powerful tool that runs in your cluster and grabs everything it needs from github/gitlab including:
 Container Repository Locations Helm Charts Latest Tags  It then executes the helm command as a &amp;ldquo;sync&amp;rdquo; in your cluster and puts it all together in a beautiful visual graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caddy &gt; Nginx</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/caddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/caddy/</guid>
      <description>On Caddy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UniHelm</title>
      <link>https://gantry.cloud/post/unihelm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gantry.cloud/post/unihelm/</guid>
      <description>Unifying your helm.. is it a good idea?
So you have twenty microservices floating around with their own values files, stateful sets, service yamls and possibly even pulling from isolated sources of secrets.
This can be hard to maintain, depending on your CI pipeline due to the fact that each values file needs to have its versions modified every time a new container is made, tagged and pushed to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
